## AINUN NAWWARAH BINTI ZAHARRUDIN

#### GAME PROGRAMMER

#### **Contact Info**

+6014-3394200

red.hana0515@gmail.com

https://red-hana0515.github.io/

### Soft Skills

Well-Organized Punctuality Eager to Learn

### Language

Bahasa Malaysia

Native

**English** 

Spoken and Written

Japanese

Basic Reading

### **Interests**

**Creative Writing** 

Video Editing

Horror / Mystery Genres

Narrative-based

Farming Simulation Genres

#### Reference

#### Johann Lim Tek Sen

Programme Leader of Computing and Creative Media UOWMKDU ts.lim@uow.edu.my

Yap Chin Kein

Lecturer of UOWMKDU

ck.yap@uow.edu.my

## (1) About Me

A senior college student majoring in game programming who has involved in multiple team projects. While I have few experience in certain game engines, I'm willing to learn and improve further knowledge on other game-related works, especially in the tech art department.

# **Education**

June 2020 - Current

University of Wollongong Malaysia KDU

**Bachelor of Game Development (Hons)** 

May 2019 - April 2020

University of Wollongong Malaysia KDU

**Foundation Studies of Arts and Technology** 

### **Project Experiences**

Sept 2022 - May 2023 • Final year project, made in Unity

**PASSAGE** · Tasked as 3D shader graphics programmer, VFX and UI technical artist

• https://uowmgames.itch.io/passage

Jan 2022 - April 2022 • Mobile multiplayer game project, made in Unity

**PURRPATRATOR** • Tasked as one of the mechanics programmer

https://uowmgames.itch.io/purrpatrator

Sept 2021 - Dec 2021 • First game project, made in Unity

10,000 METERS DEEP • Tasked as one of the generalist programmer, video trailer editor

• <a href="https://uowmgames.itch.io/10000-meters-deep">https://uowmgames.itch.io/10000-meters-deep</a>

### **Skillset**

UNITY **Advanced** 

C++ Intermediate

**PREMIER PRO** Intermediate